<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.example.apple.goslinglovelace.MainActivity">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView3"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        android:gravity="center_vertical|center_horizontal"
        android:text="Ada Lovelace"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="-6dp"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="0dp" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_below="@+id/textView3"
        android:scrollbarStyle="insideInset">

    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_below="@+id/textView3"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageView2"
            android:layout_width="180dp"
            android:layout_height="180dp"
            android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
            android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
            android:layout_marginStart="12dp"
            app:srcCompat="@drawable/ada_lovelace_portrait" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView4"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
            android:layout_toEndOf="@+id/imageView2"
            android:text="Throughout her life, Lovelace was strongly interested in scientific developments and fads of the day, including phrenology[49] and mesmerism.[50] After her work with Babbage, Lovelace continued to work on other projects. In 1844 she commented to a friend Woronzow Greig about her desire to create a mathematical model for how the brain gives rise to thoughts and nerves to feelings (&quot;a calculus of the nervous system&quot;).[51] She never achieved this, however. In part, her interest in the brain came from a long-running pre-occupation, inherited from her mother, about her 'potential' madness. As part of her research into this project, she visited the electrical engineer Andrew Crosse in 1844 to learn how to carry out electrical experiments.[52] In the same year, she wrote a review of a paper by Baron Karl von Reichenbach, Researches on Magnetism, but this was not published and does not appear to have progressed past the first draft.[53] In 1851, the year before her cancer struck, she wrote to her mother mentioning &quot;certain productions&quot; she was working on regarding the relation of maths and music.[54] Lovelace first met Charles Babbage in June 1833, through their mutual friend Mary Somerville. Later that month Babbage invited Lovelace to see the prototype for his Difference Engine.[55] She became fascinated with the machine and used her relationship with Somerville to visit Babbage as often as she could. Babbage was impressed by Lovelace's intellect and analytic skills. He called her &quot;The Enchantress of Number&quot;.[56][b] In 1843 he wrote to her: Forget this world and all its troubles and if possible its multitudinous Charlatans—every thing in short but the Enchantress of Number. During a nine-month period in 1842–43, Lovelace translated the Italian mathematician Luigi Menabrea's article on Babbage's newest proposed machine, the Analytical Engine. With the article, she appended a set of notes.[58] Explaining the Analytical Engine's function was a difficult task, as even many other scientists did not really grasp the concept and the British establishment was uninterested in it.[59] Lovelace's notes even had to explain how the Analytical Engine differed from the original Difference Engine.[60] Her work was well received at the time; the scientist Michael Faraday described himself as a supporter of her writing.[61] The notes are around three times longer than the article itself and include (in Section G[62]), in complete detail, a method for calculating a sequence of Bernoulli numbers with the Engine, which could have run correctly had Babbage's Analytical Engine been built.[63] (Only his Difference Engine has been built, completed in London in 2002.[64]) Based on this work Lovelace is now widely considered the first computer programmer[1] and her method is recognised as the world's first computer program.[65] Section G also contains Lovelace's dismissal of artificial intelligence. She wrote that &quot;The Analytical Engine has no pretensions whatever to originate anything. It can do whatever we know how to order it to perform. It can follow analysis; but it has no power of anticipating any analytical relations or truths.&quot; This objection has been the subject of much debate and rebuttal, for example by Alan Turing in his paper &quot;Computing Machinery and Intelligence&quot;.[66]" />
    </RelativeLayout>

    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>